And then we can move on to the next stage
Which is the summary of some of our live streams this year
Let's take a look at what live streams we've done this year
Hello, good evening everyone
We've done about 10 live streams this year
In the beginning of the year, we held an event called
Defeating Kimi
But this event only lasted for 2 episodes
One is because there are fewer people who apply for this event
I don't know if you guys know about this event
Let me explain it to you guys
This event is where we select a player from the number of players who have signed up
And then let him or Kimi pass through an event
That has no winner
And then let him or Kimi pass through a match
You guys don't know what it is right?
And then let him or Kimi pass through the match
If the person who passes the challenge has succeeded
He or she will get a 1,000 yuan gold card
If the person who passes the challenge fails
He or she will get a 500 yuan gold card
Why did this event only last for 2 episodes?
Because no one signed up
I don't know why everyone
Why is the number of people who want to participate in this event so low?
This is...
This is the event...
The content of the challenge is...
You can take a look, we had this before
This is what we did that day
We weren't singing, we were making clothes in the MD
Yeah, you can get 500 yuan of JD card
And because no one...
Because no one took part in it
You can't finish it
Yeah
But the challenge...
The challenge is that you can get 500 yuan of JD card
And...
Actually, we have been encouraging everyone
That is to say...
During the MD process
Whether you use it well or not
As long as you dare to share it
We will help you forward it
Because...
Everyone...
Next year...
There should be none this year
Because everyone...
Whether they use MD
Whether they use it well or not
When they first used it
They must have used it badly
No one is born to use MD
So we encourage everyone very much
No matter what you do
You can spread it out first
Show it to everyone
Increase the popularity of our MD
Right?
And then the second live broadcast of this year
Well...
Except for the first live broadcast of WinJimShow
It is our collaboration with AnyRadar at that time
Let's open a project file
At that time, we made a skirt like this
If you want to download this skirt
It is available in our store
Although we can't find it now
But it is available in our store
It can be downloaded for free
But I didn't add this pattern
I changed this pattern
So everyone...
This pattern may not be available
But other patterns are available
This whole set is available
Including the skirt I made in it
It's all available
This hat should also be available
Oh, the hat is not available
I took a look and I didn't put the hat on
Dangerous, dangerous
Well, this set
In fact, the main point is how to deal with these layers
In this issue
AnyRadar is to introduce to everyone
How to deal with it
How to deal with it in MD
And some subsequent updates
Including how to connect it with other 3D software
The process of these works
In this issue
In fact, the main thing everyone can see
Is to learn how to do this kind of multi-layer fabric
And how to deal with some of these problems like this
And how to do this kind of draw effect
I should have mentioned the hat in the middle
And then the next live broadcast
In the second live broadcast
The second live broadcast of this year is
To make a swimsuit
The swimsuit file
I haven't uploaded it to the store yet
I will upload it when I have time
This is the swimsuit that we wear in Hana
A set
The mouse has a loud voice
Because the mouse is closer to our microphone sound
This device is a little closer
I pull it away a little
Then do this set of clothes
Hello, CJ model network
Hello hello
The production process of this set of clothes
Is in our
The video of the draft is available
You can take a look
Learn how to make this set of clothes
This set of clothes
As long as you learn how to do
In the future, no matter what you do
Is a swimsuit
Or underwear
All can be
Then when we broadcast this issue
It was still sealed by the supermarket
The live broadcast room was temporarily sealed
Laugh to death
This set of clothes
It's not particularly difficult to sit down
Oh really
That's good
Then after this issue
After this issue
Our live broadcast is me
I'm responsible for the live broadcast
It should be the assassin set
Then the guest of that issue is Yang Pengcheng
Yang Da
Yang Da will share with you
Usually make clothes
And make those characters
The key point of that Zhezhou
There are also a lot of dry goods in that issue
Because
Our few guests who came over
Are more powerful guests
And they have different in each issue
This
How to connect to other 3D software
This set of clothes
Then the main of this set of clothes
The main content
In fact, one is how to do this kind of binding effect
And this is how to go
In the absence of reference pictures
To make this kind of
Boots and gloves
And how to do this
It's quite convenient to do this
And make a mask
The mask is not particularly difficult
This is the live broadcast
And then
In the back
This is the live broadcast
And then
In the back of the live broadcast
Oh, I also did some this year
Um, I made some teaching videos
One is
On the basis of that T-shirt
Made
A dress
Um, this is changed with a T-shirt
Uh, the inspiration of this dress is actually quite funny
It's because there was a little friend in the group
Said he didn't know how to make that dress
He said that
Um, how to make the T-shirt
Uh, changed into a dress
Well, the first point is
We have been
With the user
That is to say
Although we know that everyone is
There is no way
Everyone is just going to restore that
Uh, the painting of the T-shirt
But
Some things are not scientific
You know
Just
Some
These videos are not scientific
It's not a video
It's that
That
Uh, the painting of the T-shirt is not scientific
If you want to do it in our store
You can't just
Just do it directly
Just
You have to use some other methods
Just add some technical methods to do
What about this video
We can recommend everyone
Whether it's a novice or an old hand
You can take a look
Because in this video
I put a lot of functions
All
Is covered in it
And
This
The duration of the video is relatively short
Just looks
It's more convenient
Um
Then the next issue
The next issue
Is the Hanfu issue
The Hanfu issue
Mainly asked
This Hanfu is more
In fact
We used to have a time
About Hanfu live broadcast
But the Hanfu live broadcast
That issue
Everyone just feels it's not enough
Just no taste
No taste
Just feel
Just that Hanfu is not like Hanfu
Then I made a Hanfu of Hannah
Then this issue
This is MD9 or MD10
MD10
Made a set of clothes
Uh, in fact
This is the core function
MD9 also has
Uh, because I mainly used that
Interesting
So
Extremely
The
מש
I
I also talked about the difference between the different options of OBJ when you style your hair.
You can go and watch that video.
This hairstyle is done in MD.
It's done directly with fabric.
Actually, it takes a lot of time to make clothes.
It takes a lot of time to make details.
And then there's the motorcycle.
The guest in the motorcycle episode is...
Oh, my head is stuck.
Oh, Pan Xueteng.
Let me look for the project document.
You can choose, because I'm wearing fabric directly.
But...
Hanfu is actually very simple.
The Hanfu version is much simpler than you think.
The hair...
Because I did it directly in MD, it's definitely not detailed enough.
The hair is better done outside.
This is the motorcycle suit from that episode.
And this set of clothes can also be bought at the store.
If you want this...
If you want to buy it directly, you can go directly to the shopping mall.
Then you can put it here.
I forgot to announce this.
Anyway, if you see the live broadcast today, you can go and buy it.
This is gloves.
There are also clothes and pants.
And then I remember when I was doing that live broadcast.
My teeth hurt.
It hurts so much.
And then at that time...
Basically, it was the guest...
She helped us.
The guest was very good.
The guest from that episode.
Hello, hello.
Ranshift.
Dye.
Hello, hello.
And then in the middle, I actually prepared a dress.
But the video of that dress was not released at the end.
I can show you a project document.
A...
A dye picture.
This dye picture.
If you are interested, next year...
If you have time at the beginning of the year, you can edit this video out.
This project was suddenly miraculously misplaced.
I was too busy in the middle.
And then there will be some teaching videos.
And the release of MD11.
And I made a video of the festival.
The end is this episode today.
I will post it when I have time.
And then next, we can call our little friend, Jinmi.
Jinmi is also...
She joined our MD team last year.
She is too excited.
I don't know what she flipped.
Anyway, she flipped something.
Your phone hit the ground.
How can it be so small?
The main camera.
She flipped the main camera.
I laughed so hard.
She is angry.
It's possible.
Let her talk about what she did this year.
This year is the first time she joined the live broadcast.
The protective suit and the uniform.
The uniform.
Yes, you can just talk about it.
I will go first.
I will come back later.
You can just talk about it.
Okay.
Let me open the document first.
I finally have a chance to drink water.
Oh my god.
Where did it go?
It's云
Uncle's live broadcast.
I'm not at that age of uncle's.
This is the costume I take on the first live broadcast I do.
This is the uniform and this is the set of gold.
This live broadcast before we join you.
How to put the backpack on the model
Then let him interact with his clothes
Then change their form
Another knowledge point of this live broadcast
I remember I said
How to add arrangement board and arrangement point
Let him roll up a board
This is the white film of the suit
This suit is not difficult in general
The second live broadcast I prepared will have more knowledge points
If you are interested in this suit
You can watch the previous live broadcast video
Then
I will continue to talk about the next one
Right
This is not the beauty of my opening
This beauty is my opening
Do you have any opinions on beauty?
The previous live broadcasts have been on Bilibili
If you want to see it, you can turn it forward
This is the second live broadcast I made
The second live broadcast is mainly about
How to modify the model's body size
Through this virtual model editor
Then there is another knowledge point
How to use morph target to control
Use your model to limit the clothing
Let him have an impact on some of the clothes
There is also this model
There is also a shoe made here
But this shoe seems to be
It's okay to look at it now
It doesn't feel right now
I had a problem with this shoe at the time
But now it has been relieved
And now there is this backpack
This backpack also adds a model
Then add the model
After adding in
Also use morph target
For this outfit
Make a promise
Just press this side in
Overall, this is not particularly difficult
If you are interested, you can go back and have a look
Then this year I also made a few
A few md11 teaching videos
Just on the official website
That 10-minute video
So it feels like everyone likes to watch that kind of short one
Then the more experienced kind of video
After that, we will also consider
Do more of those
More short
But a lot of content
Video
Wait a minute
Take a look at the left side of the live broadcast
This one
Ouch
You move to this screen
I want to take a look first
Did he do that
I want to put this first
I want to let me show it
It's already
When there is beauty
There is
I want to appear when there is beauty
Hello
OK OK
This is to tell you
How can you open
Without beauty
Just
Just not very good
It's still not very good
Just tell you about next year's plans
First of all, next year
We plan to open some online courses
This is still in the planning
The main thing is that
We want to open that
Some paid online courses
That will certainly not charge you a lot of money
The result is finally 10,000 yuan a class
Hahaha
It's definitely not that
It's definitely not this kind of exaggeration
Because we used to do food rights
Do that for free
Then if we open this
If you go to class first
Then it must be as much as possible
What can be covered
What is covered
The content is definitely new
It's impossible to use the old things to fool you
Haha
Uh, but
If you charge this
We may split
That is, we will have some
Will change your homework
Then we may have less of this kind of space
What else
Maybe we will find some small pig
Help you with something
Ah, now it's just a plan
Um
Only plan
What do you mean by one billion?
We must sell a set
Just
How much is a set of courses
Then you can choose from this set of courses
Um
Online courses
Change your homework
Yes, the homework must be changed
You are not
Even if you usually have things
Throw it into the group
We also changed it
Is your file
There is a problem
You sent it to
You come to the group
Ask for this technical support
We also changed your file
Today in front of the live broadcast
I'm still changing that person's thing
Yes
It is also possible to sell according to the style
Um
We just said this
There is a plan
Did not say
The plan is already
Just
Just now
In the new file folder
That is
The state of the new file folder
Know
Um
This is the file folder
Just newly built
Ha ha
Um
Yes
This is a plan for next year
And this is next year
That is, two weeks later
There is a lottery
Ah, there is a lottery
Understand
Understand to deduct one
This is the live broadcast on January 8th
Uh
It's a user exchange conference
When the time comes, the strong song will come
Then there is another substance
That one
An artist will come
Yes
Um
When the time comes
It will be a beautiful girl's dress
Um
Understand
There is a lottery
Ah
I understand everything
Then the live broadcast form next year
And the teaching video form will change
Ha
Then you call them over
Send a demo
What about the teaching video form next year?
That is
We will put
That one
Um
We will put
Live broadcast
That is
More focused on
Calling some
That is
Guests come together to cooperate
Just let guests come and chat
How do they usually use MD
And then
What is their MD process?
Just more standardized
Because we used to be more focused on calling some
Personal designers
Or freelancers
Some designers who are freelancers
Then we hope to be able to do more
Help some
That is
Have these wishes
and some
Some friends who are disappointed
like hope to use MD
In real business
room
So
Uhm
Then
The future teaching video will be changed
always
Because now
We all talk about some
That is
Ah
Eh
That is
A set of
Clothes
Ah
But
Actually
Um
I think it's better to watch short videos, like a 10-minute course.
It's easier to get started.
If it's difficult, there might be one or two skills.
I don't want to do this every time I do a live stream.
So in the future, I will focus more on teaching you some tools or some special functions.
Instead of just doing a set of skills.
Because although skills are very common,
and there are some functions that we can use,
but to be honest,
watching a video for an hour,
whether you watch it or I watch it, is tiring.
So I will change it in the future.
Change the taste.
Next year...
Next year, I might add some more
to work with schools.
But...
But this depends on you.
If you have a school that uses MD,
don't be afraid. You can just tell me.
We are also promoting this.
You can work with schools.
We also need people who can use MD.
Do you understand?
So...
If you have a school that uses MD,
you can contact me.
But isn't it better to use a regular version?
Right?
Then it's definitely better to work with us.
Sometimes, there are some students from schools who ask questions.
After they ask questions, I will ask them.
Yes, you can go to the school to promote.
Then I will ask them.
I will say,
Hey, which school are you from?
They will be silent.
They might be afraid of me asking.
But it's not like that.
I'm just asking casually.
What school are you from?
For example, your school has a teacher who really likes our software.
Then they can totally ask us
if we have any cooperation ideas.
It's very convenient to promote this.
Because there are also many friends who watch the live broadcast.
Yes.
Oh, then you can contact me in the background.
If the team needs to use it,
if they need to buy it,
they can also contact me directly.
Yes.
There is nothing else.
It's almost the same today.
Do you have anything else you want to talk about?
Do you have anything you want to know?
The size of the team depends on the size of your team.
A team of less than five people can buy a personal version.
A team of more than five people only needs to buy a corporate version.
How to contact me?
You can text me in the background.
This account is MD official.
Or go to our QQ group.
In the QQ group.
Then contact the group.
The group is me.
The group is called Xueli.
If you want to go public,
then wait for the scolding.
I'm not scolding you now.
But if you text me privately,
I'll scold you.
Okay?
There is no internal document.
If you learn it, you become a god.
Yes.
You have to keep learning.
Even if you are a god now,
you still have to learn.
Right?
Do you have any questions?
Yes, yes.
No. 8 can come over.
Yes.
If you don't have any questions,
then we can go to the QQ group.
See you in the QQ group.
Right?
In the lower left corner,
there is our QQ group number.
The QQ group number is 860325459.
The code is HANA.
The first H is a big letter.
HANA.
Which is the name of our new little sister.
The name of the new virtual model.
If you don't have any questions,
you can rest early today.
Okay?
Tomorrow is a peaceful night.
Tomorrow is Christmas.
Christmas.
For the fashion...
For the fashion design industry,
we have a brother named Clo.
You can search for Clo.
C-L-O.
That is for fashion designers.
It's not our software.
I have to find a Clo sticker
to show you.
And that is our brother software.
Do you understand?
Just go to the B站 to follow that.
It's called C-L-O official.
Clo official.
They have a live stream next week.
It's about underwear.
If you like underwear,
you can watch that live stream.
What's the difference between Clo and MD?
Well,
Clo is not called Clo 3D now.
It's called Clo.
The main difference between Clo and MD is that
MD is for the CG industry.
Clo is for the fashion industry.
MD will have some of our CG industry,
some of the special features,
such as remodeling,
carving,
this kind of function.
And the future difference will be bigger and bigger.
There are also some new functions,
for example,
such as smart top.
There is no such thing in Clo.
Well,
Clo is more focused on
the real production of the clothes,
that is,
some functions that are related to the real production.
For example,
what kind of function is it?
it can support the insert and exit of the clothing paper.
Yes,
Clo can also be turned to the four sides.
Well,
it just can't turn to the reset grid.
Yes,
and then on the Clo side,
there are a lot of well-known brands
that use these functions.
For example,
like Adidas,
they all use it.
Well,
the main purpose of their use is
to make a connection with the clothes in the real world.
Well,
they can do some 3D clothing in the software
to test whether this clothing is really produced,
is it integrated,
is it attached.
If it is suitable,
they can directly order that
you can produce some actual clothes
according to this paper sample and the fabric,
and then we can compare it
to see if it is suitable.
If it is suitable,
I can directly do a large-scale production.
Well,
its focus must be related to the production
and the connection in the real life.
Well,
it's not the same as our software.
do you have any other questions?
Well,
if you don't have any questions,
we can wait for the MD official group to answer them.
If you have any questions,
you can also come to our group to ask.
There are also comments on the background of Bilibili.
Then,
if you just want to contact my friends,
you can directly send a private message to the background.
This account is fine.
Well,
first of all,
we need to know that
this card and non-card are relative.
The main reason for carding is that
one,
your particle diameter may be lowered too low.
Another one is that
all your versions are involved in simulation.
You didn't freeze some of the unused versions.
For example,
we usually freeze the inner layer of the clothing.
Then,
generally speaking,
the graphics card I use on my computer now is i9.
Is it 2060S or 2070?
I forgot.
The operation is also OK.
It is also relatively smooth.
For the previous period of making clothes,
don't lower the particle diameter too low.
In terms of animation knowledge,
there was a video called
animation entry call.
You can take a look at that video.
Animation entry call.
Well,
animation entry call.
When the particle diameter is opened to 7,
the card will be opened.
Well,
in this case,
you can do it at the time of the previous period of settlement,
don't lower the particle diameter to 7.
You can first lower the particle diameter to 7.
Then,
Look at the effect, is it OK?
Look at the fold distribution, is it OK?
If it's OK, then you can increase the particle ratio to 10 or 15
And then, before the final projection, you can increase the particle ratio to 7
Do you still have any questions?
If you don't have any questions, let me see
If the version is very messy, how do you distinguish the polarity ratio or the polarity ratio?
There is a tool here called Editing Principle 2D
After selecting the plate, this direction is called the golden direction
And the 90 degree direction is the tail direction
You just need to select it, and it's OK
What does it look like when the plate is done?
Let's go to 9.25, OK?
There are still 4 minutes left, if you have any questions, you can ask now
Is it the right direction for started?
It's the right direction, exactly
Let's see, what do you expect to see?
It's not that the positive direction is the value of the paper
It's that the positive direction is the value of the paper
So it's kind of like
You probably have to work on the assignment
But it's not that it's not the right direction
It only affects the 3D view, it affects everything.
And for the fineness,
the fineness is actually just a sign, you know?
This is a sign.
What will actually affect is the shrinkage.
This is what affects the 3D and 2D at the same time.
But you can see that the 3D has it, but the 2D doesn't.
Because the 2D is UV.
The UV can't follow your movement, you know?
It's still here.
How do you use fake hair?
For this kind of question, you can search in our handbook.
I believe you have magic online.
You can search in our handbook.
If you still don't know, you can go to the group and ask us.
Part of the version is kept separately as a costume.
Then you delete the other version and save it as another one.
You save this scene first, and then delete the other versions.
And then choose another one.
And then you delete the other versions.
Just save it as a costume.
How do you make the double sides or thickness when you delete?
When you delete, there will be a thickness.
OBJ
And then
there is a thickness.
Thickness means thickness.
But because we deleted the thickness,
When you delete the thickness,
There is no UV on the side of the grid.
So when you delete the side,
Your UV may have to be divided again.
Change again.
Do you have any other questions?
If you don't have any questions,
Why don't we end here today?
If you have any other questions,
You can ask us in the Q&A section.
Okay?
Why is there no one sending in the chat?
So today's...
Okay, okay.
Okay.
I'm happy to have you.
I don't understand what you mean by clothes.
But I will.
I will.
Okay?
No, I won't.
Okay.
That's all for today.
Okay?
See you next time.
Be sure to come on January 8th.
Okay?
Everyone understands.
Family members.
Okay.
If you have any questions,
You are welcome to ask in the group.
Because sometimes I can't see the group.
Jimmy will also answer.
Jimmy is also a very professional person.
Okay.
That's all for today.
See you in the next video.
Okay?
Okay.
That's all for today's video.
All right.
Bye.
Okay.
Good evening.
Service is done here.
This smear sign...
It looks that
resonance,
This is from the research左右 area.
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye
Bye bye
He's next to you
Okay, okay, okay, goodbye
Bye bye, bye bye
I wish you good health
I will definitely help you promote
Bye bye, bye bye
Goodbye
That's Jimmy
I laughed so hard, someone asked
Who are you
You've been supporting us for so long
And you don't even know who Jimmy is
Bye bye, bye bye
This is my colleague
Another member of our MD team
Jimmy, bye bye
Bye bye, bye bye
Is Jimmy a girl?
Yes, yes, I'm a boy and she's a girl
That's it, bye bye